<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>linux on Amboss-incoming</title>
    <link>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in linux on Amboss-incoming</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 14:32:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Ubuntu to version 10.04 LTS</title>
      <link>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/posts/upgrading_ubuntu_to_10.04_lts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 14:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/posts/upgrading_ubuntu_to_10.04_lts/</guid>
      <description>[[!meta title=&amp;ldquo;Upgrading Ubuntu to version 10.04 LTS&amp;rdquo; ]]
#Upgrading Ubuntu to version 10.04 LTS
I have one laptop here(mjolnir), that I&amp;rsquo;m using for my work. I installed them ~2years ago, with an Ubuntu system, because it simply worked. I tried debian, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t support all the hardware.
I did an upgrade to 9.* once and it worked quite well. Ubuntu has an Dist-Upgrade-Application, that does all the stuff for you.
When Ubuntu 10 was released, I tried the same again, but because in the meantime I installed some 3rd-party Software, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t upgrade the system without conflicts.
Because I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time to analyze these, I postponed the upgrade.
Today I started it again, and I found out, which Applications issued the conflicts. I removed them and now the upgrade is running. ~3h still left</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun with initramdisk - NOT!</title>
      <link>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/posts/fun_with_initramdisk_-_not__33__/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 08:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/posts/fun_with_initramdisk_-_not__33__/</guid>
      <description>[[!meta title=&amp;ldquo;Fun with initramdisk - NOT!&amp;rdquo; ]]
#The Phenomenon
I just inherited the care for a system. The system of SWSBO was setup by a good friend, a so called Debian-Developer, who knows what he does and has to do. Because of some ugly hardware issues he supplied the system with a custom build kernel because a year ago or so, some drivers for the suspicious hardware was not in mainline. The system is setup with LVM on the lower layer and having the single LVs encrypted with luks. I normally setup my systems the other way around(puting the encryption below the LVM) but this gives equivalent security and should work equally well, if not even better.
Nevertheless the system looked quite goot in shape but meanwhile needed some updating.
So I did.
Imagine, your system refuses to build any new initramdisk. &amp;ldquo;WTF&amp;rdquo; I thought.
Yes, update-initramfs and mkinitramfs barfs out.
 mkinitramfs: for root /dev/mapper/marte-c_root_crypt missing dm- /sys/block/ entry mkinitramfs: workaround is MODULES=most mkinitramfs: Error please report the bug  Wow! &amp;hellip; thats a thing. Of course what I can see is, that it seems to have the opinion the root-device is depending on &amp;ldquo;dm-&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; obviously missing a number at the end. But where does that come from? No information is available on how to debug this. How does mkinitramfs come to this value at all? Neither /proc/mounts nor /etc/{crypt,m,fs}tab had a rouge entry that could lead to this.
#is the source with me
So what&amp;rsquo;s happening here? Diving into updateinitramfs doesn&amp;rsquo;t bring any clue, because it&amp;rsquo;s simply calling mkintramfs with some parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing Videomessaging between Windows and Linux</title>
      <link>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/posts/doing_videomessaging_between_windows_and_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 11:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/posts/doing_videomessaging_between_windows_and_linux/</guid>
      <description>[[!meta title=&amp;ldquo;Doing Videomessaging between Windows and Linux&amp;rdquo; ]]
#Dear Lazyweb &amp;hellip;
I don&amp;rsquo;t like skype. It&amp;rsquo;s closed source. The protocol has been barely reverse engineered.
So I&amp;rsquo;d rather go with xmpp(jabber). Jabber is an quite cool protocol and there are enough clients out there, that are able to speak xmpp.
But: there has been at least 5 years in between the first Instant Messengers that could do Voice and even Videochats.
Why is it so complicated to find an xmpp-Client for Windows that&amp;rsquo;s able to do that?
I mean, come on: Windows is the base of the &amp;ldquo;just want it to work&amp;rdquo;-userbase. Skype simply does. Even MSN simply works and is preinstalled.
How can I explain a &amp;ldquo;standarduser&amp;rdquo; we have to sort out and test different xmpp-clients to have webcam and phone?
I&amp;rsquo;m using myself pidgin on linux. It has support for Voice and Audio &amp;hellip; great. Even works really well between two linux machines. But pidgin on windows? No support. Yes, there may be some reasons. Pidgin has build in Multimedia-Stuff via gstreamer subsystems. These are not available on windows &amp;hellip;
OK, look for an other xmpp-client, thats available for windows. Even tried the complete Wikipedia List of XMPP-Clients .
 Pidgin has all the plugins I&amp;rsquo;m using but can&amp;rsquo;t support Video/Audio on Windows because of no gstreamer support Miranda had a chance, but Videosupport was only proprietary and from 2006(?) &amp;hellip; Psi has only audio support, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t negotiate with linux (but it tried, at least) (BTW: This support is by an gstreamer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behaviour of SoftRAID-1 and unreliability of Harddrives</title>
      <link>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/posts/behaviour_of_softraid-1_and_unreliability_of_harddrives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 13:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.amboss-zustellung.space/posts/behaviour_of_softraid-1_and_unreliability_of_harddrives/</guid>
      <description>[[!meta title=&amp;ldquo;Behaviour of SoftRAID-1 and unreliability of Harddrives&amp;rdquo; ]]
Here a guy has written an article about the probability that you can&amp;rsquo;t read your complete disks without errors, and the handling of this event in the Software-RAID &amp;hellip;
This makes me sorrow ;(
[[!inline pages=&amp;quot;./discussion*&amp;quot; rootpage=&amp;quot;./discussion&amp;quot;]]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
